<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>angvp blog</title><link>http://blog.angvp.com.ar/</link><description>another psychonet freak</description><atom:link href="http://blog.angvp.com.ar/feeds/all.rss.xml" rel="self"></atom:link><lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 18:48:00 -0300</lastBuildDate><item><title>Goodbye Granpa...</title><link>http://blog.angvp.com.ar/posts/2014/01/goodbye-granpa/</link><description>&lt;p&gt;I am writting this post after long time ago that I used to blog, why? well.. I
feel strange about the departure of my Grand Father.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I just know that he called Angel like me, and probably Angel Joaquin, because
lot of my cousins or uncles call like that, anyway, he was father of 13~
(known) childs, and I feel so guilty that I did not met him, why? well..
basicly my dad and their brothers never count on him so they never worried
about his existance, lets face it he was not the best father on the Earth, and
I understand them, but .. who understands me? I grow up without meeting him and
the promise of my dad always was .. "some day you will meet your Gran Father
son" he failed to his promise .. and he is not feeling even bad about it, .. I
cannot even judge my Grand Father as I said maybe he was an horrible person,
but I always wanted to meet him no matter what, and check if indeed he was an
horrible person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, I cannot imagine him as an horrible guy, he made some mistakes, of
course, but I never met somebody who never made a mistake right?.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, goodbye granpa, now I know that I will not meet you in person, and this is
a lesson for fighting when you really want something, I bet that if I asked
more times to my dad instead of trust of him now I would have more to say about
my granpa and not having this emptyness about how he was or anything..&lt;/p&gt;</description><dc:creator xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/">Ángel Velásquez</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2014 18:48:00 -0300</pubDate><guid>tag:blog.angvp.com.ar,2014-01-18:posts/2014/01/goodbye-granpa/</guid><category>family</category><category>parents</category></item></channel></rss>